Hello, hello friends, welcome to Dishonor. Today
in this video we will do fundamental research of ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company Limited.
We will do this fundamental analysis for FY12, that is, the year which
ended in March 2017. We are
going to do fundamental research of that company.
For this fundamental research, we will take the
help of a microscope. If you do
not know much about it, then do
not worry because in this video
I will tell you what this packaged juice is and
how it works. I will
walk you through it and will also make a video compilation.
Friends, the microscope was started by Professor Joseph
Cross, who is a
professor of accounting at Stanford University.
Today, you
Ajay, a fundamental analyst, use this tool. The
biggest thing in this is that no
sentiment of the fundamental analyst
works in it. It has 9 criteria
and a company
gets one point for every quarter. If a company is
not able to meet any criteria, then
we give it zero points. In this way,
any company  It can achieve a maximum of 9 points,
but this is also not less than the
Vaikuntha score of 9. If a
company achieves this, it is called a company with strong fundamentals.
If a company achieves a score of 4, 5, or
6, then it is
called a company with average fundamentals. If a
company achieves a score of 0.12, then
it is complete and these are fundamental
companies. So here we start
this video and see what is the
performance of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited with the score of petrol and whether it is an
Everest company or is it a fundamental
company. But here you can see that there are
three categories on your screen.
We will mix its channel in three rounds
and the first round is profitability, in
which there are four criteria and in this the
company can get up to 4 points. Let us
see what the company does. The
first criterion in the front row is
possible net income. If the company has positive net
income in March,  For the 2017 version, we'll give
it one point. It's very simple.
Here, the company
generated net income from these commercials, 100, 193, 560.
As you can see in your sketch, the
first column contains the figures for March 2017, and the
second one for March 2019. We're
concerned with Twenty20 cricket matches. Here,
we see that this company
generated an amount of 193, 8.7 crore from Bigg Boss. So, we
give the company one point. Now, let's move on and
look at our second criteria, which is the
positive and debit, meaning the return on income should be
positive this year.
So, we checked the company's data
sheets and saw that the company's return as of March
2019 is 3.2%. Thus,
it's positive. The company has
presented its history. So, we
give the company this point. Now, let's
move on to our third criteria, which is
positive.  Operating Cash: If the
operating cash of this company is positive, then we will give
one point to the company. So, here we
check what has happened. We
went to the company's website and
downloaded their castor moderation as
you can see and here we saw
that here is its figure which is 3432
points
quot crore, this 031, that I have converted it,
so here the company has generated a positive
operating castor, 340 and
32.824, for we can say that the company has
developed Ishq Tere and we
give one more point to the company. Now we move ahead
towards our last criteria, friends, the
fourth criteria here is a little
cautious and it says that we should reduce the gas from
operations with later ton, that is, the
castor moderation which we have just
calculated in the third criteria should be more than the
net income of the first criteria.
If the
castor is more, then only we will put the company on one side.
If it is not, then we will
give zero points to the company. So we  Let's check
what happens with the company here.
Here we are seeing that the cash is in
operation Shri 1008 and the
amount of its profit is
93.6. In this way, we can say that the
change from operations is
more than the net income. So, in this way, we
give the company a full point here
and the company gets
four points in profitability. Now we go to
my screen and in the profitability round in Madrid, Spain, we
give the company more points. Now
we update it and it becomes the
fourth of the company. So, this was
after the first round, ICICI Lombard
General Insurance Company Limited,
Fundamental and Stripes, for ₹5.
Now we go to our second category,
in the second round, which is leverage. There are
three categories in it. When you look on the screen,
which are those three categories,
which are the liberation criteria for
physics.  We will look at the criteria
and the first criterion here is '
long-term ratio'.
Friends, from here the
method of calculation will
change a little and the words we will get here will be '
lower' and 'high'. This means that now
we have to compare and compare with the previous year's data.
So we have to see
that the lower ratio of long-term capital
currency, that is, our long-term
effect, should be less than last year's.
Only then will the company get a fiat phone. So we
will compare it with the 2019 figure. Here we
see that Sachin's test wicket total is
0.09, which has become 0.08 after reduction. So in
this way, one new point has been
gained here because the
long term presented in it has been reduced and our
difference has been reduced. So we give
one point to the company and moving ahead, our second
area close which is high current ratio
in current, that is, current rate 0A should be
present.  It should be more than last year,
so we check what has happened for
both the years. We saw that
last year it was 0.5 points and now it has become
20 points, which means it has decreased.
Here the company has
not been able to fulfill this condition again, hence we will
not give any points to the computer in its test carrier
and we have zero
points here and moving ahead to the third
and final criteria of leverage, which is
tuition tuition of laptop, means that if the company has issued
any new issue, then
we can say to the company that the company has
issued equity shares and in such a case
we do not give any points to the company.
So here we
went to their website and looked at one thing called castro financing.
We saw that they had issued some shares vital
and as you
can see in your figure, Khatri under-51, that they have issued
dry air, so here we do
not give any points to the company. The Finance Minister has
downloaded one of his tweets and we give
zero points to the company. In this way, we give zero points to the
company in leverage.  We give it one
point and update it in our score.
After the period, the company's performance is reduced.
Now we
move ahead and look at our third round,
which is operational efficiency. There are only
two criteria in this. We see
how the company performs. The first
criterion is hard cross market
and the profit margin or profit, which we
call simply profit margin, should be
higher than the previous year. So we check
how the company has performed in this.
Here we are seeing that in
March 2018, the profit margin was 9686 percent,
which has decreased and is 24.48 percent. So
what is the difference in Twenty20 matches, so this has decreased
and hence we will
not give any points to this company here and the company
gets zero points. We come forward and
we look at our ninth criterion and
operational efficiency. The second criterion will be the
final criterion. To
check the fundamental position of the company, here this  The
criteria is that the hydrocarbon
turnover ratio, that is, the average number, should be
higher than last year. Chapter
14: So, we check what happened here.
We checked that the last year's
turnover ratio was 5.06%, which has
now become 5.42%, and there has been
an increase in it. So, here we will
give one point to the company, and in this way, as soon as the
company gets 108 here, the company gets
one point in operational residency.
In the third round, we update the ground
and we update the company's overall
score here, so everything becomes
six. So, friend, a complete
score has been entered here. And as
I told you earlier, if a
company gets a score of four, five, or six, then
that company is above an average
company. So, we can say that
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company Limited is a fundamental
company with 5.06% in 2011. How did you like this video?
If you liked the video  If you liked it then please
like and share it and if
you have not subscribed to our channel yet then
please subscribe to our channel
and press the bell icon thank you
[Music]